<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"
    "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">

<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
  <meta content="text/html; charset=us-ascii" http-equiv="content-type" />
  <title>@PLUGIN_KEY@ Plugin</title>
  <link rel="stylesheet" href= "../../plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/pluginhelp.css" type="text/css" media= "screen" />
</head>

<body>
<div class="help">
  <h1>@PLUGIN_KEY@</h1>
  <p>Plugin Version @PLUGIN_VERSION@</p>
  <hr style="margin-left: -10px; margin-top: 10px; height: 1px; width: 100%; color: #5981BD;" noshade="noshade" />

  <p>Liquibase is an open source tool to manage database changes. You can find
    more information at
    <a href="https://www.liquibase.org/">https://www.liquibase.org/</a>.</p>

  <h2>ElectricFlow Integration to Liquibase</h2>

  <p>The plugin interacts with the Liquibase command-line tool
    (liquibase).</p>

  <h2>Integrated Version</h2>

  <p>This plugin was developed and tested against version 3.6.2.</p>

  <h1>Plugin Procedures</h1>
  <p>IMPORTANT: For all of the following parameter descriptions, the required
    parameters are in <span class="required">bold
    italics</span>.</p>

    <div id="CreateConfiguration"><a name="CreateConfiguration" id="CreateConfiguration"></a>

    <h2>Plugin Configuration</h2>

    <p>Plugin configurations are sets of parameters that apply
        across some or all of the plugin procedures. They are
        intended to reduce repetition of common values, create
        predefined sets of parameters for end users, and to
        securely store credentials where needed. Each configuration
        is given a unique name that is entered in designated
        parameters on the procedures that use them.<br />
        Plugin configurations are created in ElectricFlow by going to
        the "Administration" tab and then to the "Plugins"
        subtab. The "Configure" link is on the right side of the row for the
        specific plugin, which will open the Configuration page.
    </p>
    <table class="grid">
      <thead>
        <tr><th>Parameter</th><th>Description</th></tr>
      </thead>
      <tbody>
        <tr>
          <td class="required">Configuration Name</td>
          <td>Provide a unique name for the configuration.(Required)</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td>Description</td>
          <td>Provide a meaningful description for your configuration.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td class="required">Database Driver</td>
          <td>Driver string based on the type of database to which you want to
            connect.(Required)</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td class="required">Database string</td>
          <td>The jdbc string to open a connection to your database.(Required)</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td class="required">User Name</td>
          <td>Provide the user login ID. Login IDs are case sensitive. (Required)</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td class="required">Password</td>
          <td>Provide the user-specified password. (Required)</td>
        </tr>
      </tbody>
  </table>
  <img src="../../plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/images/createConfiguration.png" alt="form" /></div>

  <div id="runLiquibase"><a name="runLiquibase" id="runLiquibase"></a>

  <h2>runLiquibase Configuration</h2>
  <p>This is the generic liquibase wrapper for the command line tool. The format
    of the command passed is as follow:<br />
    liquibase [options] --driver DRIVER --changeLogFile FILE --username USER --password PASS COMMAND_and_PARAMS'</p>
  <table class="grid">
    <thead>
      <tr><th>Parameter</th><th>Description</th></tr>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
      <tr>
        <td class="required">Configuration Name</td>
        <td>The name of the configuration that contains the information to
          connect to the database server. (Required)</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td class="required">Liquibase location</td>
        <td>Path to the liquibase command-line tool. Path must be abosulte if the
          tool is not in the agent user PATH (Required)</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td>Options</td>
        <td>Additional options to pass in front of the command.</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td class="required">Changelog location</td>
        <td>Absolute path to the changelog.xml file containing the changesets.
           Relative path is calculated from the job workspace. (Required)</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td class="required">Liquibase command</td>
        <td>Command to run followed by its parameters. (Required)</td>
      </tr>
    </tbody>
  </table>
  <img src="../../plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/images/runLiquibase.png" alt="form" /></div>

  <h1>Release Notes</h1>
  <h2>@PLUGIN_KEY@ 1.0.0 </h2>
  <ul>
      <li>Initial version.</li>
  </ul>

  <h1>Contact authors</h1>
  <ul>
    <li>Laurent Rochette (<a href="mailto:lrochette@electric-cloud.com">lrochette@electric-cloud.com</a>)</li>
  </ul>

  <h1>Legal Jumbo</h1>

  <p>This module is free for use. Modify it however you see fit to better your
  experience using ElectricCommander. Share your enhancements and fixes.</p>

  <p>This module is not officially supported by Electric Cloud. It has undergone no
  formal testing and you may run into issues that have not been uncovered in the
  limited manual testing done so far.</p>

  <p>Electric Cloud should not be held liable for any repercussions of using this
  software.</p>
</div>
</body>
</html>
